ACTWU's Organizing Department Records. 5619/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Orientation Kit J. P. Stevens Campaign, 1976 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- Legal. Civil No. 1201 Decree, 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Legal, 1967-1970 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Legal, 1965-1967 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- ACTWU, 1976 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- J. P. Stevens Directory (Box 109, Folder 7)
- Social Justice, 1977-1979 (Box 109, Folder 8)
- J. P. Stevens, 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 9)
- J. P. Stevens Annual Report, 1979 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Social Justice, 1977-1978 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  No. 5, 6, 14 and 15
- Directory of Numbers and Information, 1977-1978 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- J. P. Stevens. Social Justice. Fact Sheet, 1977-1978 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- ACTWU Leadership Packet. Fact Sheet, 1974 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Sensitive Statistics Information, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Social Justice, 1977 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  Number 11-12
- J. P. Stevens Documents, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- ACTWU Papers/Forms [folder 1 of 3] (Box 110, Folder 8)
- ACTWU Papers/Forms [folder 2 of 3] (Box 110, Folder 9)
- ACTWU Papers/Forms [folder 3 of 3] (Box 110, Folder 10)
- Getting the most from the court's remedies, 1977 (Box 110, Folder 11)
- Stevens Orientation [folder 1 of 2], 1970-1977 (Box 110, Folder 12)
- Stevens Orientation [folder 2 of 2], 1970-1977 (Box 110, Folder 13)
- ACTWU. Fruit of the Loom. Company Material, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 14)
  Spanish & English
- ACTWU. Fruit of the Loom. Union Material, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 15)
- ACTWU. Union Material, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 16)
- ACTWU. Newsletters (Box 110, Folder 17)
- ACTWU. We say Union Yes (Box 110, Folder 18)
- ACTWU. Insurance (Box 110, Folder 19)
- ACTWU. Company Scare Tactics (Box 110, Folder 20)
- ACTWU. First Contracts (Box 110, Folder 21)
- ACTWU. Blitz (Box 110, Folder 22)
- ACTWU. Guarantee, 1995 (Box 110, Folder 23)
- ACTWU. Meeting Announcements (Box 110, Folder 24)
- ACTWU. Hearings (Box 110, Folder 25)
- ACTWU. Victory, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 26)
- ACTWU. Cartoons (Box 110, Folder 27)
- ACTWU. The Union Difference (Box 110, Folder 28)
- ACTWU. Contract Survey (Box 110, Folder 29)
- Organizing Probe (Box 110, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 110, Folder 31)
- ACTWU Organizing Institute, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- George Meany Center for Labor Studies. Textile Workers Union of America, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Memorandum from Barkin and Baldanzi, 1939-1942 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Solomon Barkin, 1943-1976 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Central States Joint Board, 1960 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Information reported by ACWA Affiliates, 1975-1981 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Various Union Publications, 1986-1988 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- J. P. Stevens, 1978-1980 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- J. P. Stevens Advertising, 1978-1980 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- J. P. Stevens Research Dept., 1976-1979 (Box 111, Folder 10)
- Organizing Kit for J. P. Stevens Campaign, 1977 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- J. P. Stevens. Speeches, Letters, and Statements [folder 1 of 2], 1979 (Box 111, Folder 12)
- J. P. Stevens. Speeches, Letters and Statements [folder 2 of 2], 1979 (Box 111, Folder 13)